I got news from Hirogato, one of my favorite spandex catsuit brands.
They launched a new sub-brand called Neoskin and they're doing catsuits with prints in awesome colors.
So stay tuned, I'm going to show them to you.
So they got new boxes.
Oops.
And...
These are wrapped.
it is really really bright color white all of them what i love and this is the purple one and also
a part of the outfit is this really big hood you can put on top of it so i'm going to try it
really curious because this looks like huge. I love huge hoods. It looks very tiny but I know the
fabric is stretchy so I hope I will fit inside and I'm going to change. This is the purple one and
the print is bright acid green and Hirogato used a new screen printing technique here using a
silicon print which is like a bit raised so you have kind of a relief feeling so you can actually
feel the print it's a bit sticky and they added these distressed scratches so to say so it looks
a bit more used and it adds to the cyberpunk flair of the whole suit
this is also it looks like a GPU so really tech wear e-girl vibes and just a whole
yeah different look than the usual Hirogato suits the trademark Hirogato cat is here of course no
Hirogato suit without a cat and I love the different design things so we have a barcode
here we have something like a loading bar here that says prototype although these suits are
called version 1.0 so I don't know maybe there will be more versions and more looks in the future
we have this um signs here on the spine I don't know what they say actually maybe someone can tell
me and yeah contour stitching here and we have a front zip so Stefan I really like that you should
do that more now looking forward to more Hirogartner front zip catsuits when I open it
and it's a different look and I really like it
The fabric itself is the already well-known Hiro Gato Satin Spandex.
I also have a purple satin spandex catsuit, normal one.
And I just love this because it's just so smooth and it feels so luxurious and comfy.
For the Neo Skin Collection, there is an additional item.
the assassin's hood in the same color than the suit and i think i just have to like put it on
like a hood put it on first i think i have to close the zipper again
okay so we have like a triangle in front here like points here and here and here
and a really really big hood which is reinforced in the front so it falls really nicely it looks
really cool definitely looks like an assassin hood
enough with the purple one because there are more color options available we have a black with a
neon yellow which i think is my favorite and there's also this light blue with some kind of
peach orange and I'm going to change into I think the black one first.
I'm trying to read everything that's printed on the suit. So here's bio interface module
do not interfere and here we have like energy output stable. It reminds me of a Pikachu Pokemon
with the energy blitz blizzard what is blitz lightning lightning and yeah this suit is really
cool as well oh just something else and of course the leg
thanks I also saw that we have the country stitching here for me like an
arrow down the bum which is also nice and figure shaping and here's a trick
what I like to do before I put on such a catsuit because they can feel a little
bit tight in the beginning I like to let me just put that off here I like to
pre-stretch the fabric and I go inside the legs or the arms with both hands and
then simply stretch it out a bit and move it a bit around so the fabric can
pre-stretch before you put it on which makes putting it on way easier
especially with the legs. Arms up, mostly not a problem. So I'm going to close the
zipper. I think I prefer the one with the open zipper for these suits. Again I
I love the front zip here and I closed it because I'm going to put on the hood here as well
and wringing everything like this
and I'm putting on the hood
I love these kind of big hoods I think they're the best kind of hoods they look so badass and
I mean they're called Assassin's it and that's what you get
Like all the rogues and assassins and all the games are always having like these big kind of hoods because it makes you more mysterious
and badass
I am going to open the zipper again with the hood on
because I think with the hood going down here it always creates like a keyhole look
also look so yeah I think it's really cool I think you can wear that to go out and party
for I don't know goth parties you can go to a comic convention or gaming convention with this
kind of outfit if you don't want to do like a cosplay or something. This looks
really cool and badass and you will definitely stick out of the crowd
especially with all the neon prints here. And now for the last part I'm going to
change into the bodysuit. This is the third color option I'm going to show you.
This light blue with orange and there's a fourth color option available if you
don't want to know what that is check out the Hirogato web suit. I linked in
the description text use my discount code if you want to order something
there there is a hood available for this as well of course but I'm just going to
show you the bodysuit real quick so yeah we have a really high cut here in the
legs I think trying to decide what my favorite color combination is of course
since I love black I personally prefer the black one but I also like the purple
one I mean I also got the purple one as a normal satin spandex catsuit from
Hirogato because I think that color is just so beautiful and also the material
is just so cool I really love the satin spandex if you don't want to have all
these prints there are the satin spandex catsuits and bodysuits available without
prints again check out the hero got a web page not web suit yeah you can tell
me in the comment which one you like the most and also how do you like the new
design I love it I think it's really cool I really dig it so yeah I also
really love the neon colors I think they pop okay so yeah check out my channel
My other Hirogato videos, I've got a bunch of them with a lot of different catsuits, different materials, different patterns.
And yeah, have a look there. Have a look in the description text where I write everything down.
Have a look at my Patreon if you want to support me on my other socials.
I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye.